Guide to the Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
Hunt, Violet papers, 1858-1962.
- Series I. Family
  - 2. Ford family (Brown/Hueffer)
    - a. Correspondence
      - ii. General correspondence to the Ford family
        - National Portrait Gallery Offices -- June 20, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 25-d)
          With receipt for the portrait.
        - North London School of Drawing -- May 31, 1853 (Box 5, Folder 26)
          North London Sir, We the undersigned take this opportunity/
          Signed by the members of the class.
        - Rathbone, [Harner?] -- Mar. 1, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 27)
          Birkenhead My dear Mrs Hueffer I am very glad you/enjoyed
        - [Rossetti, Lucy Brown] -- Mar. 23 [n.y.] (Box 5, Folder 28)
          AL[copy] to Mrs. Robertson
          [3 St. Edmund's Terrace, Regent's Park, N.W.?] Dear Mrs Robertson, The enclosed list/gives,
          Lucy Brown Rossetti, the wife of William Michael Rossetti, was Ford Madox Ford's aunt.
        - Rossetti, William Michael, 1829-1919. -- [Apr. 11, 1882] (Box 5, Folder 29)
          Envelope to Francis Hueffer
          [London]
          With another envelope, with note written on it by Violet Hunt concerning the letter, which was later sold.
          William Michael Rossetti was Ford Madox Ford's uncle.
        - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- Dec. 19, 1878 92 (Box 5, Folder 30-a)
          Cheyne Walk, S.W. My Dear Cathy Hueffer How good of you to/keep me in mind,
        - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- June 13, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 30-b)
          Chelsea My Dear Hueffer I send you the poem/D.G.R. spoke
        - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- Oct. 8, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 30-c)
          Ayrshire My Dear Hueffer I brought your History
        - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- June 29, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 30-d)
          Ayrshire My Dear Hueffer. How good of you to/send me
        - Smith, George, 1824-1901. -- Apr. 29, 1880 (Box 5, Folder 31)
          15, Waterloo Place, S.W. Dear Sir It is, I think, due to you that I
        - Trollope, Anthony, 1815-1882. -- July 17, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 32)
          39, Montagu Square Dear Sir, The enclosed is a paper
        - Watts-Dunton, Theodore, 1832-1914. -- Dec. 29, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 33)
          The Pines, Putney Hill My dear Hueffer I cannot tell you with/how much
        - Whitechapel Art Gallery -- Jan. 26, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 34)
          1 King's Bench Walk Madam I have met with very/considerable success
    - b. Documents (by individual, then by title)
      - Brown, Emma Hill Madox, 1834-1890. -- Oct. 20, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 35)
        AD [bill for funeral]
        Bill from James Parsons to Ford Madox Brown for Emma Brown's funeral.
      - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- 1862-1875 (Box 5, Folder 36)
        AD Account book
        84 ll. + 1
        Volume with white vellum cover and latch.
      - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- Feb. 28, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 37)
        ADS ["Labour" and another unnamed painting] -- [contract]
        Signed agreement between Ford Madox Brown and John Callow Knight, on behalf of the late Thomas Edward Plint, for a painting which is here called "Labour" though it was ultimately called "Work," and another unnamed painting.
      - Hueffer family -- 1721 (Box 5, Folder 38)
        ADS
        In German.
        Written on vellum and signed Carl VI.
      - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- Mar. 28, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 39)
        ADS Koeniglich Preussischen theologischen und philosophischen Akademie zu Muenster--[diploma]
      - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- Nov. 5, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 40)
        [contract]
        Agreement between Francis Hueffer and Charles Robert Tennant.
      - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- Mar. 12, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 41)
        ADS [receipt for burial plot]
        Receipt made out to Catherine Hueffer for the burial plot in St. Pancras Cemetery, Finchley, for her husband, Francis Hueffer.
      - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- July 6, 1872 (Box 5, Folder 42)
        D [printed] & [printed] "Richard Wagner and the Music of the Future"-- [invitation and ticket to lecture]
        Lecture given by Francis Hueffer on July 20, 1872 at the Mathematical School, Eton College and hosted by Oscar Browning.
- Series II. Correspondence
  - 1. Violet Hunt to Ford Madox Ford (by date)
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1910-1911] (Box 6, Folder 1-a)
      [n.p.] What does this mean from the Lyceum? Elsie?
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-b)
      [n.p.] Fragment I had a long talk with Mrs Clifford to day.
      With annotations in Hunt's hand.
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-c)
      [n.p.] ...two? The one about my getting to bed at 10
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-d)
      [n.p.] Dearest. Not a sign have I had from Humphreys.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-e)
      Smeeth Hill, Ashford, Kent Dearest, I am writing a line from here- as soon as I arrived
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Sunday morning, 23rd [ca. 1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-f)
      [n.p.] My dear dear Ford. I think I write awful letters always, in such
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-g)
      [n.p.] Dearest Ford. Yes, I suppose I was too busy-
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-h)
      [n.p.] Darling. I think you more than ever a genius
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-i)
      [n.p.] ...ten days! Last night, clad in sober black
      With carbon copy and later typed copy, all but the latter with annotations in Hunt's hand.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-j)
      [n.p.] Dearest. Why did I worry you? Why did I serve Humphreys
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-k)
      [n.p.] Dearest. I wish I didn't seethe justice of your arguments
      With fragment of an earlier typed copy.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-l)
      My dear. I like my place, deep down in your heart and I shall
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Monday, 31 [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-m)
      [n.p.] My dearest, my darling. How can I have depressed you?
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Tuesday, 25 [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-n)
      [n.p.] Dearest. What do you think I have done with your Reminiscences?
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Thursday evening [1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-o)
      [n.p.] Dearest. My hand shakes so. I don't know why.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Tuesday [early 1910] (Box 6, Folder 1-p)
      [n.p.] Dear Ford. I am just off to the doctor's. Silvia has written
      With TL [copy], Silvia Hunt Fogg-Elliot to her sister Violet Hunt, [n.d.], concerning why Silvia's daughter Rosamund cannot stay with Hunt.
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- June 14, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 2-a)
      [n.p.] Dear, You replied in the Westminster with such effect to a belated/ question
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Sept. 28, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 2-b)
      [n.p.] Dear darling Ford. My life seemed to stop at 8 o'clock sharp yesterday morning
      With annotations in Hunt's hand, including a note that this is her first letter to Ford after leaving Marburg on the previous day.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. October 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-c)
      [n.p.] Not a long letter, darling Ford, I am filled with
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. October 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-d)
      [n.p.] Dearest. I can't quite make out your telegram. There is no such word
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Oct. 1 [1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-e)
      [n.p.] I don't know where you are. I have sent one long letter to Marburg
      Written from a postcard.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. October 3, 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-f)
      [n.p.] I can't read very well your p.c. from your new address.
      With TL [copy], Curtis Brown & Massie to Ford Madox Ford, October 3, 1910.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Oct. 4, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 2-g)
      [n.p.] I did propose to E.H.A. what you said,
      Written from a postcard and sent to Ford in Giessen.
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. October 11, 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-h)
      [n.p.] Darling. I send you Shakespeare and some photos. Shall I send you
      With TL [copy], Demetia Kenneth Brown to Hunt, October 11, 1910.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [Oct. 15, 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-i)
      [n.p.] Dear Ford. Just a line. I am all right-
      Written from a postcard and sent to Ford at 29, Nordanlage, Giessen.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. October 15, 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-j)
      [n.p.] Dear, Answer this! I suppose you can't, alas!
      With TL [copy], Mrs. E.A. Smedley to Ford, October 15, 1910, inviting him to the Christina Rossetti Centenary dinner.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. October 21, 1910] (Box 6, Folder 2-k)
      [n.p.] This what Mr. H. says he would write
      With TL [copy], The English Review to Ford Madox Ford, October 21, 1910. Written and signed by Austin Harrison.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Oct. 21, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 2-l)
      [London] Dearest. I am writing in Humphrey's office.
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-a)
      [n.p.] ...won't have it. I won't nor will I store it or destroy it
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-b)
      1, Cloisters, Temple, E.C. I squared Mrs. Low, I think. She went out murmuring,
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-c)
      [n.p.] Dearest, I am appalled- I stay appalled. Eighteen months!
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-d)
      [n.d.] I read a little of Mr. Sorell
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-e)
      [n.p.] Dearest. The dentist says I must have a tooth out without delay-
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-f)
      The New Victorian Club, 30a, Sackville Street, Piccadilly, W. Dearest love. I have got half an hour
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-g)
      [n.p.] Dearest. You see I am being very good.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-h)
      [n.p.] Dearest. When will you get this? I can't tell.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Monday [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-i)
      [n.p.] Dearest Ford, my very heart, you are. Don't be cross & compare me
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Wednesday [ca. November 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-j)
      [n.p.] Dearest. The business letter- mine- went off this morning.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [Nov. 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-k)
      [n.p.] I have taken a type-written copy of this
      With TL [copy], The London Magazine to Ford Madox Ford, November 1910. Written and signed by Comyns Beaumont.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [Nov. 10, 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-l)
      [n.p.] This is about what I wrote to S.
      With TL [copy], Violet Hunt to Silvia Hunt Fogg-Elliot, [ca. November 10, 1910], and TL [copy], Rosamund Fogg-Elliot Wilkinson to her aunt, Violet Hunt, [n.d.].
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. December 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-m)
      [n.p.] Dearest, darling. I am so sorry for you, and you are so sorry
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. December 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-n)
      Dearest. I think it will take me all the morning
      Concerned in part with the publication of Ford's story "Riesenberg" and other writings.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. December 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-o)
      [n.p.] Riesenberg. No, dearest, don't sit in any safety valve
      Concerned in part with the publication of Ford's story "Riesenberg."
      Mentions going to Spa, Belgium on the 9th.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. December 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-p)
      [n.p.] Reisenberg. Dearest. Can you- or will you let me shorten "Riesenberg"
      Concerned with publication of Ford's story "Riesenberg."
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Tuesday morning [ca. December 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-q)
      Dearest. Let me be quite serious. I am awfully sorry it vexes you
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Thursday morning [ca. December 1910] (Box 6, Folder 3-r)
      [n.p.] Dearest. I'm so glad you like the story.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-a)
      [n.p.] R.[osamund] has written a stupid heartless letter,
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-b)
      [n.p.] Dear. Will you execute this as quickly as you can
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-c)
      [n.p.] Dearest darling, They say you are charming!
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-d)
      [n.p.] Dearest. Mrs. Low has been telephoning - She has
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-e)
      [n.p.] Lempriere say that...Dearest. Just a line.
      2 ll. + 4
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford (continued) -- [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-e)
      With a second typed copy and a carbon copy, done on a different typewriter (and earlier?), the latter with annotations in Hunt's hand.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Friday night [ca. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-f)
      [n.p.] Dear darling. Don't mind the Lyceum Club
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-g)
      [n.p.] Dearest. What can I write to you in 20 minutes? The carriage
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-h)
      [n.p.] 53. I have got my revise proofs and I want you to send me
      With the carbon copy and another typed copy, done on a different typewriter (and earlier?).
    - TL [copy, frag.] to Ford Madox Ford -- [Feb. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-i)
      [n.p.] Fragment Dearest. Why do you get my letters all posted
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [Mar. 31?, 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-j)
      [n.p.] I'm going to tea with Roy
      With annotations in Hunt's hand and an additional sheet (AM) with notes on it.
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [Apr. 1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-k)
      [n.p.] Dearest Darling. I don't want to say anything wrong- or to upset you
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- Aug. [1911] (Box 6, Folder 4-l)
      [n.p.] Dearest. Mrs Boughton has just bounced in to tell me
    - TL [copy] to Ford Madox Ford -- [autumn 1911] 6.30. p.m. (Box 6, Folder 4-m)
      [n.p.] Dearest Ford, I've been to Lane and saw Jenkyns.
    - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [1910-1911] (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
      Photocopies of letters to Ford Madox Ford
  - 2. Violet Hunt to Others (by date)
    - ALS to ? -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 7)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W.8 Dear Sir Thank you very much for your letter
      Not sent.
      Howell material.
    - ALS to [Ashmolean Museum?] -- June 19 [1918] (Box 6, Folder 8)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W. 8 Dear Sir I do not know if you/are yet aware
      C. F. Bell, to whom this letter was most likely addressed, was the Keeper of Fine Art at the Ashmolean Museum, Oxford.
      Signed "Violet Madox Hueffer."
    - AL [card] S [init.] to Bert? -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 9)
      [n.p.] With love and good wishes from --VH What is my little Bert doing now?
      Written on the back of a printed religious card
    - AL to Mr. Burdett -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 10)
      [n.p.] Dear Mr Burdett Shall I write/to your paper
    - ALS [init.] to Annie Child -- [Oct. 4, 1906] (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Pitlochry Dear Child I have had quite/an illness here.
      Annie Child was the Hunt family parlormaid.
    - AL to Mr. Garvin -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 12)
      [n.p.] Dear Mr Garvin The Life of Howell/an Anglo-Portugese
      Draft copy?
    - TLS [init.] to Gedge, Fiske & Gedge -- Apr. 26, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 13-a-c)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W.8 Dear Sirs, I am now acquainted through the papers
      With two TLS from Gedge, Fiske & Gedge to Violet Hunt, dated April 8 and 27, 1926. All three concern Violet's friend, Lady Houston. Additional notes in Hunt's hand.
    - ALS [init.] to Margaret Raine Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 14-a)
      [n.p.] Dear Mamma I call a great/part of your letter
    - ALS [init.] to Margaret Raine Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 14-b)
      [n.p.] Dear Mamma Your absence makes/itself grieviously felt!
    - ALS [init.] to Margaret Raine Hunt -- Tuesday 4th [1891?] (Box 6, Folder 14-c)
      [n.p.] My dear Mamma I was at the Penningtons/when the paper came out with the/news
    - ALS to Sarah Sanderson Hunt -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 15-a)
      6 East Terrace, Whitby My dear Grandmamma I like Whitby very/much indeed.
      Sarah Sanderson Hunt was Violet Hunt's grandmother.
    - ALS to Sarah Sanderson Hunt -- Jan. 5, 1873 (Box 6, Folder 15-b)
      1 Tor Villas, Campden Hill My Dear Grandmother I am very sorry I did not write to you
    - TLS to the Editor of The Morning Post -- Mar. 18, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 16-a-f)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W.8 Dear Sir, Ever since the news of another problematical
    - TLS to the Editor of The Morning Post (continued) -- Mar. 18, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 16-a-f)
      2 ll. + 1 + 3 + 2
      With ALS, The Morning Post to Violet Hunt, March 16, 1926, written and signed by James Greig; a draft of the letter to The Morning Post, typed and then annotated by Hunt; and a newspaper clipping (with photocopy) about the Whistler painting mentioned in the letters. Howell material.
    - AL to Juliet Hueffer Soskice -- June 26 [1927] (Box 6, Folder 17-a)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W.8 Dear Juliet This is surely rather/dreadful
      Draft copy.
      Juliet Hueffer Soskice was Ford Madox Ford's sister.
    - AL to Juliet Hueffer Soskice -- June 23 [1927] (Box 6, Folder 17-b)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W.8 Dear Juliet Thank you very/much for your letter.
    - ALS to Eustace Strickland -- [1887-1888] (Box 6, Folder 18)
      [n.p.] Dear Euty Are you very/ill?
      On verso of share application for the Folkestone Pier and Lift Company.
    - AL to Evelyn Waugh -- [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 19)
      South Lodge, 80, Campden Hill Road, W.8 Dear Evelyn Waugh I am proud that/you should review me.
    - Hueffer, F. M. -- Jan.-Feb. 1911 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      typescripts made by Violet Hunt
    - Addie, [J.N.] -- Apr. 15, 1878 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      to A.W. Hunt
    - Brown, Ford Madox -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 2)
      to Cathy
    - Brown, Ford Madox -- [SP 9 71] (Box 26, Folder 3)
      to Hueffer, Ford Madox
    - Ruskin, John -- May 30, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      to Heming
  - 3. To Violet Hunt (by author, then by date)
    - AL to Violet Hunt -- Nov. 13 [n.y.] (Box 7, Folder 1-a)
      71 Munington Road Dear Violet With regard to the "White
    - AL to Violet Hunt (continued) -- Nov. 13 [n.y.] (Box 7, Folder 1-a)
      The letter is decorated with eight coats of arms and a miniature of "Sir Nele."
    - ALS [illegible] to Violet Hunt -- Dec. 24 [n.y.] [ (Box 7, Folder 1-b)
      London] Dear Violet I wish I could/send you
    - ALS [illegible] to Violet Hunt -- Dec. 1, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1-c)
      Herne Bay, Kent Dear Sir/ Your letter of the 29th Nov 1 l.
      Addressed to V. Hueffer.
    - A [postcard] to Violet Hunt -- [1908?] (Box 7, Folder 1-d)
      Greece
    - ALS [illegible] to Violet Hunt -- Oct. 6, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 1-e)
      79A Elizabeth Street, S.W.1 Dear Violet I have been reading/your Sidall (or is it Siddal)
    - 4 envelopes, 5 cancelled stamps -- 1867-1929 (Box 7, Folder 1-f)
    - Agate, James, 1877-1947. -- [n.d.] (Box 7, Folder 2)
      ALS to Violet Hunt
      55 Doughty St., W.C.1 Dear Mrs. Hueffer Many thanks, but I neither
    - Albany -- June 10, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      [printed] Garden Party at Albany-- [invitation]
      Albany
      Commemorating the 125th anniversary of Albany.
    - Allingham, P. A. -- Nov. 19, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 4-a-f)
      Eldon House Dear Mrs. Hueffer I have been/looking through
      2 ll. + 6
      Includes eight pages of diary entries relating to Howell and Rossetti from William Allingham's diary, as copied out by his wife, P. A. Allingham; an envelope with V.H.'s notes on it; and a postcard from Mrs.
    - Allingham, P. A. (continued) -- Nov. 19, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 4-a-f)
      Allingham to Violet Hunt, dated May 15, 1924.
    - Ashmolean Museum (Oxford) -- June 20, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 5-a-b)
      TLS to Violet Hunt
      Oxford Dear Madam Thank you for your extremely kind letter.
      This and another TLS, also included here and dated August 31, 1918, were written by C.F. Bell, Keeper of Fine Art at the Ashmolean Museum.
    - Bellavue, J. C. -- Sept. 21, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      AL [postcard] S to Violet Hunt
      Vigo So sorry I had no time/to see you before I left
    - Bennett, Marguerite -- May 21, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Suncourt Hotel, Kensington Dear Miss Violet Hunt, I have just had you rung-up
      With Mrs. Bennett's card and Violet Hunt's remarks on the letter.
    - Benson, Venice Hunt, 1864- -- [n.d.] (Box 7, Folder 8-a)
      ALS [frag.] to Violet Hunt
      [n.p.] ...think more of ones suis than/any pulpit-preached sermon
    - Benson, Venice Hunt, 1864- -- [n.d.] (Box 7, Folder 8-b)
      AL [frag.] to Violet Hunt
      Hotel Schwan, Frankfurt Dear Violet We were very much puzzled
    - Bing, Marguerite -- Oct. 11, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Venice We let our Flat suddenly/conditionally
      Signed Marguerite and Herbert Bing.
    - Messrs. Blomfield & Co.'s Trinity House Royal Studios -- Sept. 24, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 10-a)
      Hastings Dr Madam We have found the enclosed/view of Hastings.
      1 l. + 3
      Siddal material.
      With photograph [photo moved to Box 20, Folder 46] of the lodging house where Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti lived in Hastings, which was reproduced in Violet Hunt's biography of her, The Wife of Rossetti.
      With two envelopes with Violet Hunt's notes on them.
    - Bornand, Odette -- Feb. 26, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 10-b)
      AL [frag.] S to Violet Hunt
      Crosby Hall, Cheyne Walk, S.W.3 Dear Madam, I am preparing a thesis
      The letter has been ripped into three pieces, one of which is missing.
    - Bouldan, Newman -- June 28, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      TL[ copy?] to Violet Hunt
      St. James Vicarage, Enfield Highway Dear Madam In answer to your letter of Jun 13th
    - Boyce, A. A. C. -- Jan. 23, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Battersea Park, S.W. Dear Mrs. V.H. Hueffer I am sorry the letter you/wanted is not
      Siddal-Rossetti material.
    - British Federation of University Women -- Feb. 26, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      London Dear Miss Hunt - I once had the pleasure of meeting/you at Jane Harrison's
      Written and signed by Mrs. Alys Russell.
    - Brown, Emma -- [n.d.], April 28 [1929?]-January 23, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 14-a-g)
      Seven letters to Violet Hunt
      Concerning Violet's questions about whether her nurse, Emma Brown, was related to Lord and Lady Bethell.
    - Bullock, J. M. -- May? 6, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      45, Doughty Street, W.C.1 Dear Miss Violet Hunt What an admirable/article
    - Button, Maidie E. -- Sept. 17, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 16-a-c)
      3, Chelmsford Road, South Woodford, E.18 Dear Madame In reply to your letter of the 16th
      With two other ALS from Maidie Button, Elizabeth Siddall Rossetti's niece, to V.H., dated October 6 and 10, 1930.
      Siddall material.
    - Cannon Brookes & Odgers, Solicitors (London) -- Nov. 16, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 17-a)